RG 38.16.1
New York University Archives
NYU TV and Media Services Videotapes
1993-2005
RG 38.16.1
New York University Archives
33.75 linear feet
This collection contains videotapes from the NYU TV and Media Services department, part of the Division of Libraries. The videotapes come from NYU-TV and the Television Center (TVCenter), two of the three departments within NYU TV and Media Services, and include both NYU-produced and commercially produced television shows, educational programming, and recordings of NYU events from 1993 to 2005.
New York University.
Arrangement note
The items in this collection are organized into one series of videotapes.
Series I: Videotapes
Provenance
The videotapes within this collection came to the University Archives in multiple accessions from the Division of Libraries.
Scope and Content
The material within this collection comes from the NYU-TV and TVCenter departments. The NYU-TV material includes both professionally and NYU-produced television shows covering a range of television genres, including sketch comedy, soap operas, science fiction, cooking and travel, as well as educational and informational documentaries. The TVCenter material predominantly covers various Founder’s Day and Commencement ceremonies.
Separated Materials note
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Conditions Governing Access note
Access to the commercially produced recordings is restricted. NYU-produced recordings are available for viewing.
This collection is in
off-site storage
.
Biographical/Historical note
NYU TV and Media Services, part of the Division of Libraries, was founded in the early 1990s to provide cable and video production services to the university. Since its inception, it has grown to include three separate departments: NYU-TV, the Television Center, and Campus Cable. NYU-TV comprises the university’s closed-circuit channels used for information, education, and entertainment purposes and is broadcast in campus buildings and residence halls. The TV Center is home to NYU-TV and serves as the NYU community's resource for video production. Campus Cable is the multi-channel television system serving the NYU residence halls and is made up of traditional cable as well as NYU-TV channels.
Source:
NYU-TV and Media Services. "About Us." NYU TV and Media Services. http://www.nyu.edu/tv.media/about.us/.
New York University.; New York University. Library Division.; Videotapes.
- Series I: Videotapes, 1993-2005
  General note
  Barcode:
  - "Gamma 51" VHS (tapes 1-8), undated (Box 1, Reel Project 1)
    Barcode: 31142042272743
  - "Air Raid" VHS (tapes 1-17), undated (Box 1, Reel Project 2)
  - "Industry Attractions" Umatic (tapes 1-3), undated (Box 1, Reel Project 3)
  - "Offline" VHS (tapes 12, 18-35), undated (Box 1, Reel Project 4)
    Barcode: 31142042272750
  - "UNET" VHS (tapes 1-2, 6, 8, 19, 21-23, 25-34), 1992-1995 (Box 2, Reel Project 5)
  - "Fast Forward: Contemporary Science Fiction" VHS (tapes 1-16, episodes 53-71, 75-79, 91), 1994-1997 (Box 3, Reel Project 7)
    Barcode: 31142042272768
  - "Bay State" VHS (tapes 1-2, 4), undated (Box 3, Reel Project 8)
  - "Children's Television Workshop 'Ghostwriter'" Umatic (tapes 2-3), 1992 (Box 2, Reel Project 6)
  - "Promos" VHS (tapes 1-3, 6, 8, 10, 13-15, 20, 22, 26-28, 31, 33-36), undated (Box 3, Reel Project 9)
  - Burly Bear Network VHS (tapes 1-19B), 1997-1998 (Box 4, Reel Project 10)
    Barcode: 31142042272776
  - "Avery Fischer Center Promo" Umatic (tapes 1-2), 1991 (Box 5, Reel Project 11)
    Barcode: 31142042272784
  - "NYU Founders Day" VHS (tapes 1-2), April 20, 1997 (Box 5, Reel Project 12)
  - "Legislative Advocacy: How to Effectively Communicate with Elected Officials" VHS, undated (Box 5, Reel Project 13)
  - "European Teleconference" VHS, April 24, 1997 (Box 5, Reel Project 14)
  - "King Juan Carlos of Spain" VHS, April 9, 1997 (Box 5, Reel Project 15)
  - "Deaf President Now: The Pulse of the People" VHS, undated (Box 5, Reel Project 16)
  - "Dialog On-Line Seach" Betamax SP (tape 1), December 5, 1995 (Box 5, Reel Project 17)
  - "Emerging Writers" Betamax SP (tapes 1-3), December 8, 1994 (Box 5, Reel Project 18)
  - "Gallatin Graduation" 1 VHS, 1 Betamax SP, 1 Master (tapes 1-3), 1997 (Box 5, Reel Project 19)
  - "Andrea Sherman Lecture" Masters (tapes 1-3), undated (Box 5, Reel Project 20)
  - "C-Team Traning Session" Betamax SP (tapes 1-3), February 20, 1996 (Box 5, Reel Project 21)
  - "C-Team B-Roll" Betamax SP (tapes 1-2), March 26, 1996 (Box 5, Reel Project 22)
  - "Distance Learning" VHS, Master (tapes 1-2), March 9, 1996 (Box 5, Reel Project 23)
  - "Mary Anne and B. Roll" Hi-8 (tapes 1-2), undated (Box 5, Reel Project 24)
  - "Assistive Technology" Betamax SP (tapes 1-3), May 3, 1996 (Box 5, Reel Project 25)
  - "Interview with President Oliva" Betamax SP (tapes 1-4), August 8, 1995 (Box 6, Reel Project 26)
    Barcode: 31142042272792
  - "DeWitt Clinton Award Dinner for Morris Sullivan" Umatic-S (tapes 1-5), December 18, 1992 (Box 6, Reel Project 27)
  - "Dukakis Cam 2" Umatic-S, August 11, 1998 (Box 6, Reel Project 28)
  - "Reel to Real: Jeff Lipsky" Master (tapes 1-2), undated (Box 6, Reel Project 29)
  - "Deconstruction Roundtable: Jacques Derrida" Master (tapes 1-2), undated (Box 6, Reel Project 30)
  - "President's Service Awards" Master (tapes 1-2), 1996 (Box 6, Reel Project 31)
  - "Commerce and the Net" Master (tapes 1-2), December 1, 1995 (Box 6, Reel Project 32)
  - "Interview with Vandana Shiva" Master, March 23, 1992 (Box 6, Reel Project 33)
  - "AmeriCorps Convocation" Master, October 14, 1994 (Box 6, Reel Project 34)
  - "Mentoring USA" Betamax SP/Master (tapes 1-2), September 1996 (Box 7, Reel Project 35)
    Barcode: 31142042272800
  - "Dialog Studio Shoot-Bobst Library" Master, December 6, 1995 (Box 7, Reel Project 36)
  - "Patterns of Adjustment" Master (tapes 1-40, undated (Box 7, Reel Project 37)
  - "SHTEIG-95" 1 Betamax SP/ 3 Master (tapes 1-4), undated (Box 7, Reel Project 38)
  - "NYU Earth Summit" Master (tapes 1-4), March 27, 1992 (Box 7, Reel Project 39)
  - "Emerging Writers" Master (tapes 1-3), undated (Box 7, Reel Project 18)
  - Burly Bear Network VHS (tapes 20A-28), undated (Box 8, Reel Project 10)
    Barcode: 31142042272818
  - "Rights & Wrongs" VHS (tapes 20-45), undated (Box 8, Reel Project 40)
  - "NASA CORE" VHS (tapes 1-5), undated (Box 9, Reel Project 41)
    Barcode: 31142042272826
  - CNBC "Smart Living" VHS, October 1993 (Box 9, Reel Project 42)
  - Burly Bear Network VHS (tapes 29A-41B), 1998 (Box 9, Reel Project 10)
  - "Rights & Wrongs" VHS (tapes 46-59), 1996 (Box 10, Reel Project 40)
    Barcode: 31142042272834
  - "Fast Forward: Contemporary Science Fiction" VHS (tapes 16-26), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 7)
  - "Meet the Professor" VHS (tapes 1-3), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 43)
  - "Exploring the Internet: Part 2" VHS (tape 2), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 44)
  - "Video Art and Virtual Reality" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 45)
  - "Goals 2000" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 46)
  - "Building Partnerships" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 47)
  - "Colour Connections" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 48)
  - "Students With Disabilities" VHS (tapes 1-2), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 49)
  - "Work Spirit" VHS (tapes 1-2), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 50)
  - "Office of the Presidency" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 51)
  - "Peace Corps Teleconference" VHS, undated (Box 10, Reel Project 52)
  - "New York Windows" VHS (tapes 3, 7, 9-16), undated (Box 10, Reel Project 53)
  - "Off the Cuff" VHS, undated (Box 11, Reel Project 54)
    Barcode: 31142042272842
  - "Career Services" VHS, 1992 (Box 11, Reel Project 55)
  - "Eggplant" VHS, undated (Box 11, Reel Project 56)
  - "NYU Student Voice on Campus" VHS (tapes 1-19, 21-29), undated (Box 11, Reel Project 57)
  - "UNET" VHS (tapes 37-43, 47-49), 1994-1996 (Box 11, Reel Project 5)
  - "Career Connection" VHS (tapes 1-3), undated (Box 11, Reel Project 58)
  - "CCTV" VHS (tapes 1-5), undated (Box 11, Reel Project 59)
  - "NYU Law Forum" Betamax SP (13 tapes), September 21, 1998 (Box 12, Reel Project 60)
    Barcode: 31142042272859
  - "Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing Development Conference" VHS and Betamax(6 tapes), June 1999 (Box 47)
  - "Works In Progress" Betamax (4 tapes), 1999 (Box 47)
  - "The 3rd Annual Schmio Awards" Betamax (4 tapes), April 1999 (Box 47)
  - "Best Nursing Practices in Care for Older Adults: Incorporating Geriatric Content into Undergraduate Education and Staff Development" (1 tape), June 1999 (Box 47)
  - "Charlie's Family Portrait WABC" Betamax, February 1999 (Box 47)
  - "Albany Day" VHS (12 tapes), 1997-1998 (Box 48)
  - "Publication of Stone and Steel" Betamax (3 tapes), March 1998 (Box 48)
  - Dean Daly Stern Betamax, 25 March 1998 (Box 48)
  - Ehrenkranz School of Social Work Advocacy Orientation Betamax (2 tapes), 23 July 1998 (Box 48)
  - "Yale Strom-Hot P'Stromi" VHS (2 tapes), November 1998 (Box 48)
  - "Alix Kates Shulman" Betamax (3 tapes), October 1997 (Box 48)
  - "Highlight Loop" Betamax(2 tapes), 1998 (Box 48)
  - "Digital Libraries Bobst" Betamax (9 tapes ), 1998 (Box 49)
  - "HeadStart Teleconference" Betamax (4 tapes), 1997 (Box 49)
  - "Interviews" (1 tape), Undated (Box 49)
  - "Peter Campus - Art Gallery Meet the Professor" Betamax (1 tape), Undated (Box 49)
  - "Cinema TV Master Original" U-matic (1 tape), October 1996 (Box 49)
  - "Beyond Race by Paul Sniderman" Betamax (1 tape), 24 Feb 1997 (Box 49)
  - "The Dental School Project" Betamax & VHS (3 tapes), Undated (Box 50)
  - "NYU Winter Stock Footage" Betamax (1 tape), Undated (Box 50)
  - "Gender Bender" Betamax & VHS (4 tapes), November 1996 (Box 50)
  - " Black Genius Series - Angela Davis and Spike Lee" (2 tapes), 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - "The Neil Brownbag Speech" Betamax VHS (2 tapes), Undated (Box 50)
  - "Internet Future" VHS (1 tape), June 1997 (Box 50)
  - "Richard Maass Lecture" Betamax (2 tapes), Undated (Box 50)
  - European Teleconference: European Union and American Union U-matic (6 tapes), 24 April 1997 (Box 50)
  - "Things To Do In Denver When You're Dead" U-matic (1 tape), November 1995 (Box 50)
  - "Club Fair Loop" VHS (1 tape), Undated (Box 50)
  - All University Sing Betamax and U-matic (6 tapes), 1994-1998 (Box 51)
  - 55th Institute on Federal Taxation: Legislative Highlights Betamax (2 tapes), 29 Sep 1996 (Box 51)
  - NYU Gospel Choir U-matic, 12 Dec 1996 (Box 51)
  - Black Genius Betamax, U-matic, & VHS (4 tapes) (Box 51)
  - Soaring to Excellence: You and the Internet VHS (Box 51)
  - Hillary Rodham Clinton NYU Americorp VHS, 9 April 1997 (Box 51)
  - King Juan Carlos of Spain NYU VHS, 9 April 1997 (Box 51)
  - Protecting Your Campus from Crime: Challenges and Solutions VHS, 17 Nov 1997 (Box 51)
  - Asian American Conference VHS, 1997 (Box 51)
  - "Bobst Library: The Heart of the University" Edit Master #3 Beta SP, 1994 (Box 52, Reel Project 6)
  - Soaring to Excellence VHS (4 tapes), 3 March 1997 (Box 52)
  - Culture and Poverty in the Clinton Era Betamax ( 4 tapes), 10 Feb 1998 (Box 52)
  - TW Cable U-matic, Undated (Box 52)
  - Stern Business School Conference Guest Speaker U-matic, 23 April 1997 (Box 52)
  - Works in Progress Betamax, 10 March 1998 (Box 52)
  - Defending Ourselves Against the Seductions of Eloquence Neil Postman Betamax, 16 Feb 1994 (Box 52)
  - What it Means for New York City Betamax, 18 June 1996 (Box 52)
  - Award Dinner Articles Betamax, Undated (Box 52)
  - OJ Verdict NYU Students Reacts Betamax, 3 Oct 1995 (Box 52)
  - Boxing After Dark VHS (Box 52)
  - NYU: Life in the Greenwich Village VHS (Box 52)
  - Summer in Paris VHS, 1996 (Box 52)
  - Fair Use Guidellines Satellite Downlink VHS, 20 Feb 1997 (Box 52)
  - Dancing With Change VHS, 05 Dec 1997 (Box 52)
  - The City and the University VHS (3 tapes), Undated (Box 53)
  - Spike Lee Lecture @ Tishman Auditorium, 18 Oct 1996 (Box 53)
  - The Helping Hand VHS (Box 53)
  - Nursing PSA Betamax, 28 April 1995 (Box 53)
  - Science at NYU Betamax, Undated (Box 53)
  - Yale Strom - Hot P'Stromi Betamax, 11 Nov 1998 (Box 53)
  - Wagner Labor Archives Betamax (2 tapes), 20 Oct 1995 (Box 53)
  - Evening Magazine U-matic, 28 Sept 1998 (Box 53)
  - Tamiment Oral History Gil Greene U-matic, 23 Jan 1991 (Box 53)
  - Post Operative Recovery Betamax, 14 June 1994 (Box 53)
  - Video Production Center Betamax, 28 Mar 1994 (Box 53)
  - The Telecommunications Act of 1996: What it Means for NYC" Betamax, 18 June 1996 (Box 53)
  - Leslie Harris Interview Betamax, Undated (Box 53)
  - Dr. Peskin Heart Warren Weaver Hall U-matic (Box 53)
  - Andrea Sherman Lecture U-matic, 24 June 1997 (Box 53)
  - Campus Media Shots U-matic, Undated (Box 53)
  - Media Services Compilation Tape U-matic (Box 53)
  - Ken Roth @ NYU U-matic, 18 Sept 1995 (Box 54)
  - Fort Lauderdale Film Festival Trailer U-matic, Undated (Box 54)
  - Kristen Linklater @ NYU U-matic, 9 Oct 1995 (Box 54)
  - "The Time is Out of Joint" Jacques Derrida Speech U-matic (2 tapes), 7 Oct. 1993 (Box 54)
  - Americorp Convocation U-matic, 14 Oct 1994 (Box 54)
  - Mary Gordon @ NYU U-matic, 02 Oct 1995 (Box 54)
  - Seward Park Conflict Resolution Class Simulation U-matic, Undated (Box 54)
  - Video Production Center U-matic, March 1993 (Box 54)
  - Dialog Final Master Betamax, Undated (Box 54)
  - King Juan Carlos in Bobst Betamax, 09 April 1997 (Box 54)
  - Women's Health # 3 Betamax (Box 54)
  - Law School Blank U-matic (Box 54)
  - Dunbar Michael Dorf Knitting Factory, 16 Nov 1998 (Box 54)
  - Questioning Media with Neil Postman Betamax, 11 July 1996 (Box 55)
  - Benefits Seminar Betamax (2 tapes), Undated (Box 55)
  - Social Work Orientation Web Site Betamax (2 tapes), 25 Aug 1998 (Box 55)
  - Financial Aid Project U-matic, Undated (Box 55)
  - Dr. Ruth U-matic, 1 Nov 1995 (Box 55)
  - Dukakis Press Conference U-matic, Undated (Box 55)
  - Industry Attractions Betamax (Box 55)
  - Advocacy in Social Work Betamax, July 1998 (Box 55)
  - Race, Gender, and the Role of Scholars in Contemporary American Society Betamax (Box 55)
  - Dr. Kallembach Chem Lab Laser Lab U-matic (3 tapes), March 1993 (Box 56)
  - "Old Photos of Bobst" Tape 6 Beta SP, August 1994 (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - "Hester Interview" Part 2 reel 7 Beta SP, Septemebr 1994 (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - "Bobst Exteriors still photos" Beta SP (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - Leslie Harris Interview Betamax, 22 April 1997 (Box 56)
  - On-going Recovery Prgram 4 Betamax, Undated (Box 56)
  - Heart Shaped Video Box U-matic, 3 Feb 1994 (Box 56)
  - Triangle Waistshirt Footage U-matic (Box 56)
  - The Return of the Hollywood Studio System U-matic, 29 Oct 1996 (Box 56)
  - Americorps Conference on Conflict Resolution Training for Grad Students U-matic (Box 56)
  - End of Training Conference Clinton Cutaways U-matic (Box 56)
  - New York University Benefits Office Developing a Savings Strategy VHS (Box 56)
  - New York University School of Law VHS (Box 56)
  - Stone and Steel Fales Library VHS, 3 March 1998 (Box 56)
  - Regional Assitance Center Video Conference VHS, 31 Oct 1996 (Box 56)
  - Health Services Grand Opening Betamax, 9 March 1998 (Box 56)
  - Woman Kind Betamax, 30 March 1996 (Box 56)
  - Long Distance Learning Seminar (Box 56)
  - Integrating Media and Instruction VHS, 1994 (Box 56)
  - Andrea Sherman Lecture VHS, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - New York University Benefits Office Developing an Investment Strategy VHS, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Steven J. Gould Accidental Human Presence in the Age Bacteria, 16 Oct 1996 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Last Takes of Catherine AFC Shots Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "NYU Animal Training" Dub Master Betamax, 4 Oct 1994 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "AFC and Library Pick ups and Mike Part 1" Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Ivo Ezeta NYU-Tv Anim" Betamax, June 1995 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Yale Strom Hot P'Stromi " Betamax (2 tapes), 4 Nov 1998 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Mike Marcinelli Pt. 2 Dana at Nursing Workstation" Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Interview with Kassandra Goins; Tuff Gong; Jamaica Segment; Anastasra Bard/Claudine Athens" Betamax, 17 July 1997 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "NYU Science Video Dub of 1st Part" U-matic (3 tapes), Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Black Thought in Progress Angela Y. Davis" Betamax, 18 Feb 1994 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Industry Buzz # 2 Chinatown" U-matic, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Media/Power/Culture Navigating Between Apocalypse and Utopia in a Digital Era" U-matic, 12 Nov 1996 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Corporate Takeover of News: Blunting of the Sword Anastasia Bard" U-matic, 8 Oct 1996 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Sir Harold Acton Lecture" Betamax, 4 Feb 1999 (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Presidents Team Community Volunteer" Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Academic Activism Conference" Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Improving Science" Betamax, Undated (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "Video Production Center Orientation Video Tape 23" U-matic, Undated (Box 58)
  - "William Baker at NYU" VHS, 6 Nov 1995 (Box 58)
  - "The MacArthur Tapes" Betamax (2 tapes), 14 Feb 1994 (Box 58)
  - "Ar9-9-94 Tape 1,2,3," Betamax (3 tapes), 9 Sep 1994 (Box 58)
  - "Dialog B-Roll" Betamax, 6 June 1996 (Box 58)
  - "Dialog On-Line Search" Betamax, 5 Dec. 1995 (Box 58)
  - "NYU Varsity Club Dinner, 1996 Hall of Fame Inductees" VHS, 12 Oct. 1996 (Box 58)
  - "Derrida Pre-Lecture Audience & Keynote Part 2" Betamax, Undated (Box 58)
  - "Mhoriocks Spork" Betamax, Undated (Box 58)
  - "C-Span School bus" Betamax (2 tapes), 29 Feb 1996 (Box 58)
  - "Benefits" Betamax (2 tapes), Undated (Box 58)
  - "1968 Revisted" U-matic, 14 Oct 1993 (Box 58)
  - "L.J. Oliva - College Athletics" U-matic, Undated (Box 58)
  - "Riot Footage 60s Civil Rights Abuse Hearings" Betamax, Undated (Box 58)
  - "CCUMC and Lower Indicators for NYU TV" Betamax, Undated (Box 58)
  - "Constant Stranger" Betamax, Undated (Box 58)
  - "Wager Archives Tape 3" Betamax, 20 Oct 1995 (Box 58)
  - "Dr. Peskin - Heart" Betamax (2 tapes), 5 March 1993 (Box 58)
  - "T.I. School of Social Work" Betamax, 9 March 1998 (Box 59)
  - "Arlene Krab" Betamax, 9 March 1998 (Box 59)
  - "NYU Health Center Grand Opening" Betamax (2 tapes), Undated (Box 59)
  - "C-Team" Betamax (5 tapes), 1996 (Box 59)
  - "Bobst Library Tape 1 & 2" VHS, 28 April 1998 (Box 59)
  - "Study Center Dedication" VHS, 20 Sep 1991 (Box 59)
  - "Derrida" Betamax (3 tapes), Undated (Box 59)
  - "Hillary Rodham Clinton Americorp" Betamax, 9 April 1997 (Box 59)
  - "Cantor Film Center Convocation" Betamax, 15 Oct 1997 (Box 59)
  - "Dedication of the James Hester Wing Bobst Library" Betamax, 7 Nov 1994 (Box 59)
  - "Women's Health" Betamax (3 tapes), Undated (Box 59)
  - "NYU Student Productions Sigfriend and Roy Raw" Hi8, Undated (Box 60)
  - "NYU Festival" Hi8 (3 tapes), 24 Nov 1998 (Box 60)
  - "Lesli Harris Interview Tape 2" Betamax, 22 April 1997 (Box 60)
  - "Welcome to NYU" VHS and U-matic (2 tapes)
  - "Air Raid" VHS and U-matic (4 tapes), Undated (Box 60)
  - "Gamma-51" Betamax and U-matic (3 tapes), 1993-1994 (Box 60)
  - "NYU Gospel Choir" U-matic (2 tapes), 1996 (Box 60)
  - "NYU Press Book Spots" U-matic, Undated (Box 60)
  - "Industry Attractions" U-matic, Undated (Box 60)
  - "(Your Name Here)" Betamax and U-matic (2tapes), Oct 1994 (Box 60)
  - "Science at NYU" VHS, April 1994 (Box 60)
  - "Festival Spring Orchestra and Symphony Orchestra Fall Concert" Betamax, 24 Nov 1998 (Box 61)
  - "The City and the University" Betamax, 26 Sep 1994 (Box 61)
  - "Save the Day Mathematics Education: The Debate Over the Standards Tape 1" Betamax, Undated (Box 61)
  - "The Artist as Advocate Tape 2" Betamax, 6 Oct 1998 (Box 61)
  - "Ann Linnchan Roll-Ins" Betamax, Undated (Box 61)
  - "Olympics Opening Ceremony" VHS (3 tapes), 15 Sep 2000 (Box 61)
  - "Library Success in the New World" VHS, 23 April 2000 (Box 61)
  - "In Our Own Words" VHS, Undated (Box 61)
  - "On our Own Terms: Moyers on Dying" VHS, 18 April 2000 (Box 61)
  - "NYU Tonight Election 2000" VHS (Box 61)
  - "NYU Celebrates 2000" VHS, Undated (Box 61)
  - "NYU Law School: Rally against Impeachment" VHS (2 tapes), 14 Dec 1998 (Box 61)
  - "African Studies Readings" Betamax (3 tapes), 1998-2000 (Box 61)
  - "Mental Health in the Year 2010" Betamax (2 tapes), 1 April 1998 (Box 61)
  - "NYU Press Awards" Betamax, 18 April 2000 (Box 61)
  - "New Open" Betamax, 3 Nov 1995 (Box 62)
  - "Dr. Judy @ Z-100" Betamax, 25 Sep 1996 (Box 62)
  - "Ed Koch" VHS, Undated (Box 62)
  - "Promo Masters" Betamax, 21 June 1995 (Box 62)
  - "NYU TV News" Betamax, Undated (Box 62)
  - "Anniversary of Attica Riots" VHS and U-matic (2 tapes), 1996 (Box 62)
  - "Advances in Science" U-matic, Undated (Box 62)
  - "Corporate Takeover of News: Blunting the Sword" U-matic, 8 Oct 1996 (Box 62)
  - "The Electric Blanket" U-matic, Undated (Box 62)
  - "NYU University Week Wide of Service" U-matic, Undated (Box 62)
  - "STU Camera 1 Shimon Peres" Betamax (2 tapes), Undated (Box 62)
  - "Sheer Realities" Grey Art Gallery (5 tapes), 28 Feb 2000; B-Roll of exhbit, Exhibit Voice overs, (Box 64)
  - "Bamboozled" NYU Institute of African American Affairs (2 tapes), 2 Nov 2000 (Box 64)
  - "Doctor Ruth", 01 Nov 1995 (Box 64)
  - "Dr. Ferrara at NYU" (3 tapes), 2000 (Box 64)
  - "Inverted Odysseys" (4 tapes), 22 Nov 1999 (Box 64)
  - "Faculty Focus Interviews" McSorleys, Village Writers, Great Depression, Undated (Box 64)
  - "Jump Tomorrow" Joel Hopkins and Tundi Adibimpe (2 tapes), 17 Jul 2001 (Box 64)
  - "Panel Discussion Art and Alternative Media", 7 Feb 1998 (Box 64)
  - "Accidental Human Presence in the Age of Bacteria" Steven J. Gould, 16 Oct 1996 (Box 64)
  - "Bradford Marshalls Interview", undated (Box 64)
  - "Integrating Media and Instruction", 1994 (Box 64)
  - "A Night of Langston Hughes" with Danny Glover and Ossie Davis, undated (Box 64)
  - "Dale Russakoff Speech", 3 Jun 1999 (Box 64)
  - "Irish Paintings" Grey Art Gallery, 29 Jun 1999 (Box 64)
  - "Walter Mosley and Ranall Robinson at NYU Law" (2 tapes), 10 Feb 2000 (Box 65)
  - "NYU Law Panel #3" (3 tapes), 21 Sep 1998 (Box 65)
  - "Morning on the Millenium Panel", 14 Apr 2000 (Box 65)
  - "Democracy and the Rule of Law in a Changing World" Lecture (4 tapes), 10 Mar 2000 (Box 65)
  - "Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing Development", 2 Jun 1999 (Box 65)
  - "My Country vs ME", 13 Feb 2002 (Box 66)
  - "Art Museums and the Public Trust: A Deontological...", 8 Apr 2003 (Box 66)
  - "A Evening with Marvin J. Miller", 21 May 2003 (Box 66)
  - "Marketing on the Internet" Evening Lecture Series (5 tapes), 7 Oct 1999 (Box 66)
  - "Merryl Lynch Digital Lecture", 23 Jan 2000 (Box 65)
  - "Our Democracy, Our Airways", 30 Sep 2002 (Box 66)
  - "2001 Mayors Election Conference", 8 Nov 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Rekindling Reform", 10 Mar 2003 (Box 66)
  - "Real Anatomy: Frumkes and O'Neil", 18 Nov 2002 (Box 66)
  - "Raineri Lecture in Ancient Studies", 13 Jun 2001 (Box 66)
  - "ACH-ALLC 2001 Conference" (3 tapes), 13 Jun 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Teaching More Effectively with Technology" (3 tapes), 11 Apr 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Cirriculum Base Parent Program", 9 Mar 2001 (Box 66)
  - "1 Commerce", 6 Apr 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Progress and Paradox: The Realities of Globalization" (4 tapes), 14 Jan 2003 (Box 66)
  - "Julian Schnabel Interview" (4 tapes), 7 Oct 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Dean's Day" (2 tapes), 5 Apr 2003 (Box 66)
  - "At Your Library - Nancy Kranich", 14 Mar 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Beowolf Shoot", unknown (Box 66)
  - "The Alger Hiss Story", 21 Mar 2001 (Box 66)
  - "September 11, Announcements" John Beckman, 11 Sep 2001 (Box 66)
  - "President's Welcome 2005", 5 Sep 2005 (Box 66)
  - "Looking Back, Looking Beyond" (3 tapes), 25 Sep 2003 (Box 66)